[{
	"Question": "What does Coot-tha (Ku-ta) mean in Turball indigenous language?",
	"answerA": "Trees",
	"answerB": "Bees",
	"answerC": "Honey",
	"answerD": "Koala",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What is the artist's surname?",
	"answerA": "North",
	"answerB": "South",
	"answerC": "East",
	"answerD": "West",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "What type is the spikey tree?",
	"answerA": "Fire-stick",
	"answerB": "Floss-silk",
	"answerC": "Fairy-floss",
	"answerD": "Devil-spike",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What is this snake made from?",
	"answerA": "Garden hose",
	"answerB": "Pool noodle",
	"answerC": "Car muffler",
	"answerD": "Lollies",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What lives here?",
	"answerA": "Wombat",
	"answerB": "Bilby",
	"answerC": "Echidna",
	"answerD": "Bandicoot",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "What's his name?",
	"answerA": "Dave",
	"answerB": "Gary",
	"answerC": "Bruce",
	"answerD": "Greg",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What are fungi great at?",
	"answerA": "Partying",
	"answerB": "Camouflaging",
	"answerC": "Recycling",
	"answerD": "Swimming",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "3, 5, 1, 8 =",
	"answerA": "BEAD",
	"answerB": "CAGE",
	"answerC": "FADE",
	"answerD": "FACE",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "How many bats in the band?",
	"answerA": "3",
	"answerB": "4",
	"answerC": "5",
	"answerD": "6",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What bonsai style is this?",
	"answerA": "Cascade",
	"answerB": "Windswept",
	"answerC": "Formal upright",
	"answerD": "Informal upright",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{
	"Question": "How many stone lanterns in the Japanese Garden?",
	"answerA": "3",
	"answerB": "4",
	"answerC": "5",
	"answerD": "6",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "Where was the Japanese Garden originally located?",
	"answerA": "Dreamworld",
	"answerB": "World Expo 88",
	"answerC": "Surfers Paradise",
	"answerD": "Chinatown",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What type of native bees are here?",
	"answerA": "Honeypot",
	"answerB": "Pollensack",
	"answerC": "Sugarbag",
	"answerD": "Bluebox",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "What are their names?",
	"answerA": "Ju and Zhu",
	"answerB": "Shu and Chu",
	"answerC": "Spots and Dots",
	"answerD": "Cindy and Bobby",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "What type of fern is this?",
	"answerA": "King",
	"answerB": "Monster",
	"answerC": "Jumbo",
	"answerD": "Giant",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
},
{	"Question": "How many red leaves are here?",
	"answerA": "3",
	"answerB": "4",
	"answerC": "6",
	"answerD": "8",
	"correctAnswer": "C"
},
{	"Question": "Where is this type of Agave from?",
	"answerA": "Spain",
	"answerB": "Mexico",
	"answerC": "Italy",
	"answerD": "Portugal",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "Where is this type of cactus from?",
	"answerA": "South Africa",
	"answerB": "South America",
	"answerC": "South Asia",
	"answerD": "South Australia",
	"correctAnswer": "A"
},
{	"Question": "What type of plant is this?",
	"answerA": "Aguve",
	"answerB": "Agave",
	"answerC": "Cactus",
	"answerD": "Palm",
	"correctAnswer": "B"
},
{	"Question": "What is this person trying to catch?",
	"answerA": "Fish",
	"answerB": "Yabbies",
	"answerC": "Bees",
	"answerD": "Butterflies",
	"correctAnswer": "D"
}
]